Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Ontario Federation of Labour (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: To the: Medical Services Insurance Enquiry, 1964; Publication (Box 127, Folder 1)
    Author: Ontario Federation of Labour
    Notes: 2 copies
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: To: Royal Commission on Health Services, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 1)
- Ontario Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in Ontario, a submission to the Gov. of Ontario, 1961; Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Submission of the Ontario Federation of Labour., 1966; Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
    Notes: Mar. 1966
  - Item 3: Submission of the Ontario Federation of Labour., 1966; Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
    Notes: Dec. 1966
  - Item 4: Submission of the Ontario Federation of Labour, Special Joint Committee, 1963; Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
    Notes: Aug. 1963
  - Item 5: Submission of the Ontario Federation of Labour, Special Joint Committee, 1967; Publication (Box 127, Folder 2)
    Notes: Feb. 1967
- Ontario Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Summary of policies, 1957-1965 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Summary of policies, 1957-1970 (Box 127, Folder 3)
- Federation des travailleurs du Quebec, Publication (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Brief on unemployment submitted to the Government of the Province of Quebec, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Legislative brief submitted to the government of the province of Quebec, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 4)
    Author: Federation des travailleurs du Quebec
  - Item 3: Memoire de la Federation des Travailleurs du Quebec, 1961; Publication (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Memoire sur L'Assurance-Hospitalisation, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Federation des travailleurs du Quebec, Publication (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Workmen's compensation: Brief submitted on November 14, 1961..., Publication (Box 127, Folder 5)
- Railway Transportation Brotherhoods; Trades and Labor Congress of Canada, Publication (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Collective liability and state insurance versus private insurance in Workmen's Compensation Law, 1931; Publication (Box 127, Folder 6)
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Presentation of the Saskatchewan Federation of Labour to the Government of the Province of Saskatchewan on Legislative and other matters, 1964; Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Brief of submission to Royal Commission on Mechanics' Lien Act on behalf of Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Brief of submission to Royal Commission on Mechanics' Lien Act on behalf of Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, 1966; Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Brief of submission to Royal Commission on Mechanics' Lien Act on behalf of Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, 1967; Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Main features of Saskatchewan Labour Legislation, 1964; Publication (Box 127, Folder 7)
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Joint Brief of Alberta, Manitoba and Saskatchewan Federations of Labour, 1967; Publication (Box 127, Folder 8)
    Author: Saskatchewan Federation of Labour
  - Item 2: Policies, based on Resolutions adopted at Annual Conventions, 1956 to 1962, Publication (Box 127, Folder 8)
- Saskatchewan Federation of Labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Loaded questions and straight answers on labour, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Medical care for all, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Political Freedom for Corporations, Double Standard, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The Saskatchewan Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Wage Earners and the election, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: 12th Annual Convention, 1967; Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Labour's losses to date!, 1965; Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Saskatchewan Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
    Notes: 1965 January
  - Item 9: Security+Safety+Full employment+Common sense = 4-32, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: The First fight for Medicare, 1962; Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: The Provincial voice of labor, Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: This must not Be!, 1965; Publication (Box 127, Folder 9)
    Notes: Several articles
- UCAPAWA (United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Best workers school, 1940; Publication (Box 128, Folder 1)
    Author: United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America
    Notes: Program for a workshop
  - Item 2: Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Summary reports UCAPAWA: National Cotton Conference held Washington, D.C., Jan. 15-17, 1940, Publication (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The C.I.O. and the farmers, 1937; Publication (Box 128, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2
  - Item 5: Three resident schools for Agricultural Workers, contribute to UCAPAWA's Field Workers School Fund, 1940; Publication (Box 128, Folder 1)
    Notes: Campaigning flyer
- UCAPAWA (United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing and Allied Workers of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Tobacco workers organize !: Raise wages! Gain security! Build a strong union!, 1941; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Author: United Cannery, Agricultural, Packing, and Allied Workers of America
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Carpenters Local Unions and Councils Pension Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 128, Folder 3)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 128, Folder 3)
    Author: Hudson Valley District Council of Carpenters
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Deadly Parallel in law, 1910; Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: In the Supreme Court of the United States, October Term, 1916Paine Lumber Company, Ltd.., Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Paine Lumber Company, et .al., Complaints, against Elbridge H. Neal, 1911; Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
    Author: United States. Circuit Court (New York: Southern District)
  - Item 4: Paine Lumber Company, Limited, et al, Complainants, against Elbridge H. Neal, et al., Defendants: Complainants' reply brief, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Paine Lumber Company, Limited, et al, Complainants-Appellants, against Elbridge H. Neal, et al., Defendants-Appellees: Reply brief on behalf of Complainants-Appellants, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
    Author: United States Circuit Court of Appeals (2nd Circuit)
  - Item 6: Supreme Judicial Court for the Commonwealth ... Edward T. Reynolds v. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Carpenters' Union no. 595, 1907; Publication (Box 128, Folder 4)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Blank copy of an Agreement for Prescription Drug Plan of New York City District Council of Carpenters Welfare Fund., 1964; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Magazine articles - First in Progress; A chain of benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Manhattan Borough District CouncilCarpenters and Joiners of America - Correspondence, 1902; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Prescription drug plan of the New York City District Council of Carpenters Welfare Fund., 1964; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Report on the underfed children attending the Chicago Public Schools: with some facts and figures relating to the general conditions, and how they and their families are being aided through public and private organizations, 1908; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Your welfare fund: the New York City District Council of Carpenters, Welfare Fund, 1964; Publication (Box 128, Folder 5)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Carpentry, Instructional Unit for Safety, Publication (Box 128, Folder 6)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report: Governors' Lumber fact finding board, 1954; Publication (Box 128, Folder 7)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the General Executive Board., 1959; Publication (Box 128, Folder 8)
    Notes: May, 1959; Sept.-Nov. 1959
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Alaska carpenters health and security fund, 1956; Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Carpenters health and welfare trust, 1957; Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Carpenters health and welfare trust fund for California, Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Important valuable information, Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
    Author: Lumber and Sawmill workers
  - Item 5: Southern California Lumber industry welfare fund, 1952; Publication (Box 128, Folder 9)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: They kept ahead of the future: ... a condensed history ..., 1967; Publication (Box 128, Folder 10)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Explanation of Labor-Management Reporting ... and ... Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 128, Folder 11)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Long Beach Labor News, 1952; Publication (Box 128, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol. 31, no. 43
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Appeal of Local Union no. 376 to the membership of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1926; Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Local Union No. 376
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship standards for Carpenters, Master Builders Association of Ithaca, New York, Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Carpenters organize, organize, Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Author: Clyde Johnson
  - Item 4: Fiftieth Anniv. Of Carpenters and Joiners Local Union 309., 1909; Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners. Local Union 309
    Notes: Souvenier
  - Item 5: How to organize the job: a handbook for stewards, 1945; Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Author: United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America. Pile Drivers, Bridge, Wharf and Dock Builders. Local Union no. 34.
  - Item 6: Portable pensions - Locals' agreement protects rights of 50,000 Carpenters in New York metropolitan Area, 1966; Publication (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Notes: Industrial Bulletin, August 1966
  - Item 7: The Furniture Worker, 1927-1928 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Notes: vol. 1, no.1-4
  - Item 8: Victory through unionism, 1940-1949 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    Author: Harold G. Vatter
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your union!: the Lumber and Sawmill Workers, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1935; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Memo from the Amalgamated Society of Carpenters and Joiners, Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Memo from the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1928; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Progressive Carpenters Campaign Program, Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Report of Thomas J. Dolan delegate to the Carpenters' Convention at Fort Worth, Texas, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Resolution - [expulsions from the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America] - challenged and case won, Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Progressive Building Trades Worker, Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dues book, 1919; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Jurisdictional disputes of the Carpenters' Union, 1926; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Author: E. E. Cummins
    Notes: Reprinted from the Quarterly Journal of Economics, vol.40, May, 1926
  - Item 3: Stewards' guide for shops, mills and factories, Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: What's wrong in the Carpenters' Union?, 1925; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Author: Progressive Building Trades Worker
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Dues book, 1919; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Jurisdictional disputes of the Carpenters' Union, 1926; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Stewards' guide for shops, mills and factories, Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: What's wrong in the Carpenters' Union?, 1925; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship standards for Carpenters and Joiners, 1949; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Correspondence, memos and press releases, 1953; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Author: Association of Catholic Trade Unions
  - Item 3: Correspondence, memos and press releases, 1956; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Correspondence, memos and press releases, 1959; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: How to de-control your union of communists. [comments and info from Local 601], 1948; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Author: Charles Owen Rice
  - Item 6: Labor Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Planning for safety: a contribution to accident prevention, Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Catholic Worker, 1956; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: The Longshoreman's Labor Leader, 1954; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: May 21, 1954. 2 copies
- Association of Catholic Trade Unions, Publication (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Catholic unit hits guilt by inference, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping
  - Item 2: Encyclicals held against Taft Act, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Labor is reminded of Catholics' aid, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Union watch urged on pay standards, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Receives labor award, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Unionists to go to Rome, 1951-1953 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Financial department, 1947; Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1947-Jan, Feb, Apr, May, July
  - Item 2: Financial department, 1959; Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1959-Dec
  - Item 3: Report of Frank Duffy (annual), 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Report of Frank Duffy (annual), 1921-1922 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Report of the Committee on Constitution, 1924; Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Supplementary Report, Committee on Constitution, 1924; Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Valuable information, Publication (Box 129, Folder 6)
    Author: Frank Duffy
- UBC (United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America), Publication (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Dues book, Publication (Box 129, Folder 7)
- Car Shop Union, Publication (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Car shop dispute goes on, 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Car shop union refuses offer, 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Carshop dispute still plagues local labor scene, 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Company explains work cut, dispatch workers end strike, 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Second round of wage talks slated today between DSI and independent union, 1953-1954 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- Association of Catholic Trade Unions, Publication (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A guy's job in life, 1953; Publication (Box 129, Folder 9)
    Author: Bob Senser
    Notes: Reprinted from the September, 1953 issue of The Voice of St. Jude
  - Item 2: ACTU Newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.2, no.1,5-7 (1966-67)
  - Item 3: ACTU Newsletter, 1968; Publication (Box 129, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.3, no.4 (1968)
  - Item 4: ACTU Newsletter, 1969; Publication (Box 129, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.4, no.2 (1969)
  - Item 5: ACTU Newsletter, 1970; Publication (Box 129, Folder 9)